export default data = [
  {
      question: "Industrial waste must be carefully handled, or it will _____ the public water supply.",
      options: ["contaminate","facilitate","legitimate","manipulate"],
      correct_option: "contaminate"
  },
  {
      question: "John’s vision was direct, concrete and simple and he recorded _______ the incidents of everyday life.",
      options: ["universally","scarcely","passively","faithfully"],
      correct_option: "faithfully"
  },
  {
      question: "The government cannot find a good reason to _____ its high expenses on weapons, especially when the number of people living in poverty is so high.",
      options: ["abolish","escort","justify","mingle"],
      correct_option: "justify"
  },
  {
      question: "The writing teacher has found that reading fantasies such as J. K. Rowling’s Harry Potter may inspire her students to think and write with _____.",
      options: ["creativity","generosity","superstition","foundation"],
      correct_option: "creativity"
  },
  {
      question: "Since several child _____ cases were reported on the TV news, the public has become more aware of the issue of domestic violence.",
      options: ["blunder","abuse","essence","defect"],
      correct_option: "abuse"
  },
  {
      question: "Helen’s doctor suggested that she undergo a heart surgery. But she decided to ask for a second _____ from another doctor.",
      options: ["purpose","statement","opinion","excuse"],
      correct_option: "opinion"
  },
  {
      question: "All candidates selected after _____ screening will be further invited to an interview, after which the final admission decision will be made.",
      options: ["preliminary","affectionate","controversial","excessive"],
      correct_option: "preliminary"
  },
  {
      question: "To prevent terrorist attacks, the security guards at the airport check all luggage carefully to see if there are any _____ items or other dangerous objects.",
      options: ["dynamic","identical","permanent","explosive"],
      correct_option: "explosive"
  },
  {
      question: "In the desert, a huge mall with art galleries, theaters, and museums will be constructed to _____ visitors from the heat outside.",
      options: ["convert","defend","shelter","vacuum"],
      correct_option: "shelter"
  },
  {
      question: "Judge Harris always has good points to make. Her arguments are very _____ as they are based on logic and sound reasoning.",
      options: ["emphatic","indifferent","dominant","persuasive"],
      correct_option: "persuasive"
  },
]